A Finding Aid to the Federal Art Project, Photographic Division Collection, circa 1920-1965, bulk 1935-1942, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Artist Files, circa 1920-1965; Series 1; Archival Resource Key; 9.6 Linear feet Boxes 1-24
  - Hicks, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Higgins, Victor, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Hiler, Hilaire, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Hirsch, Willard, circa 1939-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 7)
    includes photos of Hirsch, circa 1939
  - Hoff, Guy, circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Hoffbauer, Charles, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Hoffman, Ben, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Hoffman, Seth, 1937-1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Hoglander, H., circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Holmberg, Lawrence, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Holmes, Henry, 1937-1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Holmes, Stuart, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Holston, Edith, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Holzhauer, Emil, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Hondius, Gerrit, 1937-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Hood, Richard, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Hord, Donal, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 20)
    includes photos of Hord with others including Arthur Ames, Holger Cahill, Homer Dana, Joseph Daynish, Thyris Field, Pat Fleming, Jean Goodwin, Nelson Partridge, and Stanton MacDonald Wright
  - Horn, Milton, circa 1934-circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 21)
    includes photos of Horn, circa 1937
  - Horowitz, Jacques, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Horr, Axel, circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 23)
    includes photos of Horr, 1937, 1940
  - Hovannes, John, circa 1932-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Hovell, Joseph, circa 1936-circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 25)
    includes photo of Hovell, January 1936
  - Hover, T. A., 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - How, Kenneth, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Hullenkremer, Oden, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Hulme, James Sanford, 1937-1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Hunt, Georgine, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Hunt, Thomas, 1937-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Hutchinson, Mary, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Hyun, Paul, circa 1936-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Imler, Edgar, 1936-1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Ingersoll, G., 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Irwin, Howard Lee, circa 1937-circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Ishigaki, Eitaro, circa 1937-circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 37)
    includes photos of Ishigaki
  - Jack, Mable, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Jacobi, Eli, circa 1936-circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Jacobs, Deyo, circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Jacobson, Emanuel, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Jacoby, Samuel, 1938-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Janni, Pino, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Janowsky, Bela, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Jansen, Richard, circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 45)
    photo of Jansen
  - Jefferson, Louise E., 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Jenkins, Leonard Seweryn, circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 47)
    includes photos of Jenkins, 1937
  - Johnson, Thomas Loftin, circa 1936-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 48)
    includes photos of Johnson, circa 1938
  - Jones, Joe, 1936-circa 1943; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 49)
    includes photo of Jones
  - Jones, Leon Foster, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Jonson, Raymond, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Julius, Oscar H., 1939-1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Jurls, A., 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Juszko, Jeno, circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 4)
    includes photos of Juszko, circa 1939
  - Kachinsky, Alexander, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Kadulin, Vladimir, 1940-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Kagy, Sheffield, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Kainen, Jacob, circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Kallem, Henry, circa 1938-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Kallem, Herbert, 1940-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Kaminsky, Dora, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Kamrowski, Gerome, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Kantor, Israel, 1937-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Kantor, Joseph, 1937-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Kapfenberger, Joseph, circa 1936-circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Kaplan, Joseph, 1938-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Karfunkle, David, circa 1937-circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 17)
    includes photos of Karfunkle, circa 1938
  - Karlan, Gertrude, 1937-1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Karlen, Agnes, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Karp, Ben, circa 1936-circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Karp, William, circa 1936-circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 21)
    includes photos of Karp, September 1936, September 1938
  - Katz, Hyman William, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Katz, Nathaniel, 1937-1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Katzieff, Julius, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Kauffman, Andrene, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Kaufman, Edwin, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Kaz, Nathaniel, 1937-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Kelly, Albert Sumter, circa 1936-circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Kelpe, Karl, circa 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Kelpe, Paul, circa 1936-circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Kempton, Martha Greta, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Kennedy, Simon, circa 1936-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Kerkam, Earl, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Kerwood, Venetia Drake, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Kessel, Dmitri, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Kibrick, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - King, Alexander, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - King, Daisy Blanche, circa 1937-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - King, Roy Elwood, circa 1936-circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 39)
    includes photo of King, October 1936
  - Kleiban, Lucy, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Klein, Frank A., circa 1936-circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Klein, Michael, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Kleinman, Gladys, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Klonis, Stewart, circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Kloss, Gene, circa 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Knaths, Karl, circa 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Knight, Frederic, circa 1938-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Knotts, Benjamin, circa 1938-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 48)
    includes photo of Knotts, circa 1936
  - Koerner, Daniel, 1937-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Kollwitz, Käthe, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Konzal, Joseph, circa 1938-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Kopman, Benjamin, 1938-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Kopp, Beatrice, circa 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Kormendi, Andre, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Kotin, Albert, 1937-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Kovner, Saul, 1937-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Kozlow, Sigmund, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Kraus, Romuald, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 10)
    includes photos of Kraus, circa 1937
  - Krause, Erik Hans, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Kroll, Leon, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Kubinyi, Kalman, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Kuniyoshi, Yasuo, circa 1937-circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 14)
    includes photos of Kuniyoshi, October 1940
  - Kurtz, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Lacher, Gisella Loeffler, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - LaGrone, Oliver, circa 1935-circa 1942, circa 1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 17)
    includes photo of LaGrone
  - Lahey, Marguerite Dupuz, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - La More, Chet, 1939, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Landeck, Armin, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Lane, Harry, 1939-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Laning, Edward, circa 1937-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Laning, Edward, circa 1937-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 23)
    Scope and Contents
    includes photos of Laning, 1937, 1938, 1940
  - Laredo, Victor; La Spina, N, 1941-1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Lassaw, Ibram, circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Lassen, Ben, 1938-1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Laufman, Sidney, 1938-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Laurent, Robert, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Lauson, Michael, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Lawler, Paul, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Lawrence, Jacob, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Lawrence, William H., 1937-1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Lazzari, Pietro, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Lebduska, Lawrence H., circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Leboit, Joseph, circa 1936-circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Lechay, James, 1937-1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Lee, Doris, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Leefe, Miriam, circa 1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Lehman, Harold, 1937-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Lenhard, Josef, 1937-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Lentelli, Leo, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Leurs, Golda, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Lever, Hayley, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Levi, Julian E., circa 1938-circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 44)
    includes photo of Levi, 1940 October
  - Levinson, Abraham F., 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Levow, Irving, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Levy, D., 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Levy, Josephine Frankel, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 48)
    photo of Levy, April 1939
  - Levy, Martha, 1938-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Lewandowski, Edmund D., 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Lewis, Monty, 1937-1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 2)
    includes photo of Lewis, 1938 May
  - Lewitts, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Liberte, Lewis Jean, 1937-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Lieberman, William, 1937-1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Lightfoot, Elba, circa 1937-circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 6)
    includes photo of Lightfoot, 1938 January
  - Liguori, Charles, 1937-1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Limarzi, Joseph, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Limbach, Russell T., circa 1936-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 9)
    includes photo of Limbach, 1938 January
  - Lindenthaler, Charles, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Lipshitz, Isadore, 1938-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Lishinsky, Abraham, circa 1936-circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 12)
    includes photos of Lishinsky, circa 1939
  - Lishinsky, Abraham, circa 1936-circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Litchfield, Nell; Livingstone, Ronald, 1937-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Locke, Charles, circa 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Lockwood, Ward, 1935; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Loew, Michael, 1937-1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Lo Medico, Thomas, circa 1936-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 18)
    includes photos of Lo Medico, 1938 May
  - Lomoff, Joseph, circa 1937-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Lonergan, John, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Lonsbury, Earl, circa 1936-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Lo Pinto, Ferdinand, 1937-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Lord, Francisco P., circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 23)
    includes photos of Lord, 1938 August
  - Lorenz, Howard Taft, 1937-1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Lowell, Nat, circa 1936-circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Lowengrund, Margaret, 1936-1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Lozowick, Louis, circa 1939-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Luban, Boris, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Lubin, Jacob, 1936-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Lubovsky, Maxim, 1937-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Luce, Molly, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Lucioni, Luigi, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Ludins, Ryah, circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 33)
    includes photos of Ludins, 1937, 1939
  - Luisi, Nicholas, 1937-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Lunnon, James, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Lurie, Nan, 1937-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Lush, Vivian R., circa 1936-circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - MacAdams, Edgar, circa 1936-circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Maccoy, Guy, circa 1936-circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 2)
    includes photos of Maccoy and Leonard Jenkins, circa 1937
  - MacDonald, Julian, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Magafan, Jennie, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Mahl, Claire, circa 1936-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Maldarelli, Louis, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Malderelli, Oronzio, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Maloof, Sam, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Mandelman, Beatrice, 1939-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Manfredi, Joseph, 1937-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Mangor, E., circa 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Manship, Paul, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 12)
    photo of Manship
  - Marans, Moissaye, circa 1936-circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Marcon, Julia, 1936-1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Marder, Ida, 1936-1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Margolis, David, circa 1938-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 16)
    includes photos of Margolis, 1949 May
  - Margoulies, Berta, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Mariinsky, Vaslav, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Markham, Kyra (Kyle?), circa 1936-circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 19)
    includes photos of Markham, 1937 June
  - Markow, Jack, circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Marshall, J., circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Marshall, Margaret, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 22)
    photo of Marshall
  - Martin, Robert, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Massa, Frederick, circa 1939-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Mastaglis, Dominico, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Matta, Santiago, circa 1939-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Mattei, Antionio, circa 1938-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Matulka, Jan, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Matzal, Leopold Charles, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Maunsbach, Eric, circa 1938-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Maxey, Stevens, 1937-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Mayer, Bena Frank, 1940-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Mayer, Jules, 1937-1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - McAuliffe, Florence, circa 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - McCown, Eugene, circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - McCoy, S., 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - McCrady, John, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - McGirr, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - MacIver, Loren, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - McKiernan, John, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - McMahon, Audrey, circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 41)
    includes photos of McMahon and Holger Cahill
  - McNeil, George J., 1937-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - McNulty, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Means, Elliot, circa 1938-circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Mecklem, Austin, circa 1937-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Mecklin, Hannah, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Meert, Gertrude, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Meert, Joseph John Paul, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Meiere, Hildreth, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Melicov, Dina, circa 1938-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 6)
    includes photos of Melicov, 1938 February, 1939 April
  - Meloy, Henry J., 1937-1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Metaruga, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Meyer, George, circa 1938-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Meyer, Herbert, 1936-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Michalsky, Maximilian, circa 1935-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Michnick, David, circa 1936-circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Milavsky, B., 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Miller, Barse, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Miller, Benjamin, 1937-1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Miller, Hugh, circa 1936-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Millman, Edward, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Mims, Thomas, circa 1936-circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Mira, Alfred, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Miserendino, Vincenzo, circa 1936-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Mitchell, Bruce, circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Mitchell, Henry J., 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Mock, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Mock, Gladys, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Moldovan, Sacha, 1937-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Mommer, Paul, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Montalbano, Charles, circa 1936-circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Moore, William, circa 1936-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Moran, Eliza, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Morley, Eugene, circa 1936-circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Morosoff, Vladimir, 1938-1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Morris, Carl A., 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Morris, James, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Mose, Eric, circa 1936-circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 34)
    includes photos of Mose, circa 1936-circa 1939
  - Mousseau, Roland, circa 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Moylan, Lloyd, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Mues, William, circa 1936-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Mundhenk, Oscar, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Murphy, M. Lois, circa 1936-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Murray, Hester Miller, circa 1936-circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Murrell, Sara, circa 1937-circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Muschnik, D., circa 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Myers, Jerome, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Nadejena, Lydia, circa 1937-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Nagai, Thomas, 1937, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Nagy, Frank circa 1936-circa 1939, Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 3)
    includes photos of Nagy, circa 1939
  - Nakagawa, Kikudo, circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Nakamizo, Fuji, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Nakian, Reuben, circa 1936-circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Nash, Ginerva, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Nastasi, Frank, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Naumer, Helmuth, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Neagoe, Anna, circa 1937-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Neel, Alice, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Nelson, Bruce, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Nelson, C. G., 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Nelson, Helen, circa 1936-circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Nesin, George, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Neuwirth, Morris, circa 1939-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Nevelson, Louise, circa 1939-circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 17)